[theme music playing]
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
You suffered as well.
So. we'll make them pay.
I appreciate the chance. sir…
to prove myself.
PERSONAL RECORD
PARK JIN-CHEOL
SUNG HAN-SOO
A FEW HOURS EARLIER
What do you mean?
What if we turned this
into a bigger problem? [scoffs]
INTER-KOREAN GOVERNMENT TALKS
Hmm. Gosh. what's happening
that couldn't wait?
PRIME MINISTER
DELEGATION LEADER
Sir. you've been summoned by the DPRK.
What?
What is going on?
Why do you suddenly
want to call off the negotiations?
It is simply because
the Southern authorities
are not yet prepared to engage
in meaningful dialogue.
Excuse me?
What the hell are you talking about?
You keep running your mouths
about peaceful talks and cooperation.
all while you betray our Republic
and everything it stands for.
-What did you say?
-We already know about Ri Eung Ryeong.
the former Director General
of the Intelligence Bureau.
Not only did you smuggle him
into your country.
you also assigned the Republic's
most wanted criminal as his escort.
I'm done talking to you.
Unless you hand over those two
traitorous rats to us immediately.
not only will we call off
these negotiations.
but the relationship between
the North and the South
will be changed beyond all recognition.
Contact General Jang right away.
I'm on it. sir.
EPISODE 9
ONCE A MARINE. ALWAYS A MARINE
Your mission…
has failed.
[delegation leader laughing]
Watching the South's prime minister
back down like that
was quite a sight.
He tucked his tail between his legs.
[laughs]
Thanks to you. Comrade Ju.
everything went smoothly.
I need your word
that I'll be the one to finish him.
I always keep my promises. I assure you.
Although…
no one can be aware of this
except for you.
Now that everything has been handled
through official channels.
I must say.
taking 66 out on Southern soil…
is a burden we'd like to avoid.
You don't have to worry.
[chuckling]
[Guk-cheol] What do you mean by that?
Don't take Ri Eung Ryeong out until
we've secured intelligence on the missile.
We've already failed the mission.
Are you refusing to carry out
-the orders of the PM?
-I am.
66 and Ri Eung Ryeong
will be handed over to the North Koreans.
Thing is. if 66 keeps taking matters
into his own hands…
that's got nothing to do with us.
The only thing we can do now
is sit back and watch.
We all know
that man is willing to do anything
just to see his daughter again.
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
Hey. so about Shit Cricket…
He handcuffed him. right?
Uh-huh.
Even though he knows
they're useless against Kim.
Mm-hmm.
Then I guess he doesn't need our help.
But won't it be hard for him
to make it back?
This isn't just
some local street thug he's facing.
Are you going?
Are you?
Huh?
Look. Isn't that his phone there?
-I guess he took mine instead.
-Huh?
-Did he actually take yours?
-He must have taken it.
Wow. he left that. He must be losing it.
I better go get it. right?
Of course you should.
A phone is really expensive.
[sighs] I even owe on that thing.
Then you'd better get going now!
-That little punk. When I find him…
-Wait a second!
Before we hit the road…
let's take one of these.
-What are those?
-They're good for your joints.
Seriously?
You've been keeping it all to yourself?
I'm sharing them now.
Let's go!
Where'd you park?
Whoa! Hey. what's with this car?
This? They say it's the car of the future.
"They say it's the car of the future."
Let's see what it's got.
Hold on. Isn't the hero
supposed to be the one driving?
[phone buzzing]
66 will be handled by the other team.
That's how
you get the job done effortlessly.
Now. report to both
the Southern side and the Party
that Ri Eung Ryeong and 66 were executed.
Sir. I'm on it.
Good riddance. enemy of the state.
You shit stains.
[grunting]
I didn't know you were such a big deal.
We didn't roll out the red carpet
for you last time.
What a shame.
I recall you said you'd turn yourself in.
As it happens.
the parents' meeting is not over yet.
So you're the rat
who joined forces with the North.
The only rat here is you.
The rat who betrayed his own country.
We're alike in many ways.
We're both willing to do anything
for our children.
We're good fathers.
Don't you agree?
Didn't you say you'd get rid of me
for your daughter's sake?
You should have known
I'd get rid of you for Hye-ri too.
[tense music plays]
I have plans for you.
Put him in the trunk.
[sighs]
Comrade.
Your car's really nice.
Shh. shh. shh…
Nighty-night.
Hey. I didn't come here
to help you or anything.
I came to bring you your phone.
but the gunshots were so deafening.
I got dragged in. [chuckles]
Thanks. man.
So. what are you doing next?
Ri Eung Ryeong's likely dead.
I don't think he's dead.
They wanted him alive. you know?
Really?
This guy's really something else.
isn't he?
Trying to get in bed with North Korea.
He really doesn't think twice.
You're the worst kind of jerk.
Ri Eung Ryeong. Where is he now?
Shoot me.
You wanna leave both our kids
without a father?
Shoot.
You actually did.
Let's cut a deal.
I know why you're after Ri Eung Ryeong.
If you let me live.
I'll help you find the guy.
Let's go.
If you lie. you'll regret it.
Nighty-night. Dream about me.
Hey. Han-soo.
Thanks for coming.
We have to be around
when Min-ji walks down the aisle.
Let's roll!
[melancholic music playing]
[agent] That's North Korean.
SECURITY CHECK IN PROGRESS
Let 'em through.
Don't let your guard down.
Geez. unbelievable.
What's with those guys?
-[agent 1] Huh?
-[agent 2] Do they think we work for them?
[agent 1] Just let it go.
[agent 2] Don't you think our government
is trusting them too much?
They won't even let us inside.
but they expect us to stand guard?
That doesn't make sense.
Did you forget? North Korea's
the world's most secretive country.
And their delegation is right in there.
JUHAK WELCOMES
THE NORTH KOREAN DELEGATION!
Jong Il Peak 25
has just entered the lobby.
Jong Il Peak 25 is in the service lift.
Jong Il Peak 25 is on the fifth floor.
Jong Il Peak 25
approaching the VIP reception.
Jong Il Peak 25 is entering the VIP room.
-Should I report now. sir?
-Negative. I'll report to him myself.
Ah. Comrade Director General.
you look like you're going through it.
Have you been having a hard time
away from home?
[scoffs]
Quit stalling. Get it over with now.
What is it you're waiting for?
Don't rush me. We can take our sweet time.
[scoffs]
It's in your best interest
to start revealing the missile intel
that you've been sharing with the South.
Oh. yeah. We have plenty to discuss.
Now. fill the bathtub.
How did it go?
We saw a North Korean vehicle enter
a few minutes ago.
They were carrying a fairly big bundle
of some sort.
[whirring]
[Kim] It's Ri Eung Ryeong.
[Sang-a] The MPs are stationed outside
and NIS agents are patrolling indoors.
They can access areas
where South Korean employees work.
such as the kitchen and laundry room.
But they're always under the eye
of the North Korean agents.
They'll put up a fight.
-Can I?
-Take a look.
Which floor are the North Koreans on?
The fourth and fifth floors.
The head of the delegation
must be on the fifth floor.
and the control room
must be on the fourth.
That's their way of doing things.
How are we going to get in?
Hey. we need to get in that building
virtually unnoticed.
Right. Fat chance he'll talk.
The terms are very simple.
If we get Ri Eung Ryeong with your help.
we'll let you live.
If we fail. you die.
On the resort.
there's an underground passage
with a direct path
to the Chairman's office.
It was built for emergencies.
so there's no CCTVs.
Really? Wait a minute.
it can't be that easy.
Hey. look at me when you talk.
How do we get past the barricade?
[sighs] I have clearance.
I'm on VIP duty.
Oh. it's simpler than I thought.
Once we get to the office. with the CCTVs.
we'll be able to pinpoint his location.
[Sang-a] But there's a problem.
They've shut down the existing CCTVs
and are running the ones
they installed themselves
upstairs in the control room.
We must first secure
the main control room. then.
So you take the control room
and get his position.
Then I'll focus
on getting him out of there.
Then. while you get out…
the two of us will keep 'em busy.
-Me three.
-But wait…
Simply getting him out
through the main entrance?
I don't know. It won't be that easy. man.
Yeah. you're right.
He'll get on the laundry truck
at the loading dock on the first floor.
Laundry truck?
Since laundry is my thing now. I'm on it.
The laundry truck arrives at the dock
at 19:20 hours
and leaves at 19:30 hours.
We'll only get ten minutes for the pickup.
Ten minutes. That's a small window.
Ten minutes. then.
We can pull him out to the loading dock.
We have to make it work.
Ten minutes? Man. that plan really sucks.
They communicate every three minutes.
[groans] No way. dude.
Why are you always getting so hung up
on how difficult it's gonna be?
Why do you make it worse?
Are you scared?
I'm not scared.
It's not like breaking boards…
[Han-soo] Why bring that up?
-It's not gonna be as easy as you think.
-That's enough.
I'll be on standby. just in case.
We just need to go out
the way we came in.
[Sang-a] We'll need
to pass the barricade first.
Now let's… go get prepped for tonight.
["Go! Go!" playing]
Your wound. You should hide it.
I think we're missing one.
The tranquilizer?
Using both will give us the best chance.
[grunts] That's enough.
Oh. Hey. man. sorry about that.
We're good. bro.
I'll keep you updated in case
anything changes out here.
Okay? Be careful. everyone.
It took you four shots.
[music continues]
Ah. nice and warm in there?
I hate playing rock-paper-scissors.
Hmm… You lost.
-Cheaters!
-[Jin-cheol] Just have fun.
[Han-soo] Shut up!
Why does this always happen to me?
[music continues]
[music ends]
AUTHORIZED VEHICLE
Ju Gang-chan.
he's the chairman of the resort.
Reason for your visit?
To oversee the VIP arrangements.
-Have you heard about this?
-No. sir.
Roll down the back window. please.
The Deputy Director of NS sent me.
You can verify it.
[agent] Please wait a moment.
Chairman Ju Gang-chan
came to oversee the VIP arrangements.
Please verify that
with the Deputy Director.
Yes. Got it.
Here you go.
Let them through.
[agent 2] Open it now.
[Han-soo groaning]
Ow.
Oh. my knees.
Ow. ow. ow!
Hey. wait.
Let's close it. Are you trying
to let everyone know we're here?
NO ENTRY
ACCESS RESTRICTED
ACCESS GRANTED
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL
Wow. it's fingerprint access.
Was this place built only for you? Why?
Just think it through.
People with skeletons in the closet
always make sure they have an escape plan.
-Ugh.
Ugh.
[elevator dings]
Go.
[Han-soo] Wow. this is the kind of door
you only see on TV.
Why would someone build this?
[Jin-Cheol] Because he has skeletons
in the closet.
[Han-soo] Damn!
[Jin-Cheol] Hey. guys. look. It's nice.
Want to switch offices? Huh?
We need the blueprints.
[Sang-a] Securing the station.
Three minutes.
Mm-hmm. Two minutes.
This is our only entrance. Right here.
How much?
To get to the loading dock.
we have… two minutes. I think.
-Ms. Jung. you'll be all right?
-Yeah. I've got this.
[Han-soo] I'll distract them
from the other side.
All right. if everything
goes according to plan.
we'll meet back here
at the Chairman's office.
Put that gun away. will you?
That's not how you handle a civilian.
[Han-soo] Seems fine.
And even if I scream out loud.
no one outside this room can hear a thing.
Really?
Bang!
[Jin-cheol laughs]
-Everyone. let's get moving. Jin-Cheol.
-Oh. you're no fun.
[clears throat] All right.
Hi. hi. Hi. it's me.
Send up room service.
[Nam] Everything's prepared.
[Jin-cheol] What can you send now?
[knocking]
[Jin-cheol] Yes.
Come on in.
Can you tell me your size?
I'm a 3XL. sir.
It's a little tight.
I feel awkward in this chef's uniform.
Once we find Ri Eung Ryeong.
we'll move in.
-Please. be careful.
-You too.
-[Jin-Cheol] How do I look?
-[Han-soo] You managed to squeeze into it.
[Jin-Cheol] Yeah. I did.
Now you squeeze in there.
-Oh. not again. I'm not a contortionist.
-Hurry.
Why do you keep pushing me in tiny spaces?
It's not like Mr. Park
can squeeze in there.
What am I. origami paper? [grunts]
That you can fold me at your will?
-They're always making fun of me.
-Go.
-[Jin-Cheol] Shut up.
-[Han-soo] Really?
[upbeat music plays]
[whimsical music plays]
[Sang-a] Mwah!
Damn. Are all the women in the South
that beautiful?
Whoa. she is so pretty.
[music ends]
[Ho-won] Hi. guys.
I'm here to collect the laundry.
AUTHORIZED VEHICLE
[agent 1] You may come in.
-[agent 2] Let him through!
-[Ho-won] Thanks. have a good one.
[doorbell rings]
-Who is it?
-Room service. I have your order.
Is it dinnertime already?
It's a bit early. don't you think?
Well. I'm hungry. so let's have dinner.
[grunts]
We make a pretty good team.
My knees don't seem to agree.
Control room secured.
Oh. hey! Laundry guy! [chuckles]
Don't open that one.
Start with the earlier footage.
He's not here. but if you--
-Why won't you listen?
-Hey. keep it down.
We'll never find anything
if you keep rambling like that.
Ugh. I'm really frustrated.
Can we take a look at that one?
Hey. Hey. hey. hey. hey. There.
Oh. That's the bundle we saw.
-Is he--
-Oh. let's follow them.
Where is that?
-Where is this?
-The suite on the fifth floor.
[grunting]
[water splashing]
[delegation leader] That's enough.
-[agent grunts]
-[Eung Ryeong groaning]
[Eung Ryeong coughing]
[Eung Ryeong] I've already told you
I kept my mouth shut.
I didn't tell anyone!
I haven't even met
with the Southern authorities yet!
[delegation leader]
Of course. I suppose 66
doesn't count
as a Southern authority after all.
Hmm. Carry on.
[agent 2] Comrade. sir!
[Eung Ryeong choking]
-Shit.
-What is it?
It looks like the agents who went
to deal with 66 have gone missing.
[delegation leader] Are you sure? 66…
I'm sure that he'll come here.
There are Southern operatives outside too.
so take care of him without opening fire.
-Understood. sir. You. follow me.
-Yes. sir.
[agent 1] Shall we continue. sir?
Bring him out now.
[Jin-cheol] Hey. Kim.
Kim. are you done yet?
Hey. do you really think
he can speak right now?
I should be where he is.
since I'm the best of the three of us.
There's not much time left.
-[delegation leader] Sit down.
-Jeez…
They're gonna catch on any second.
-You two. wait outside.
-Sir?
Did I make myself clear? Wait outside.
Two agents have left.
but two are still waiting outside.
Understood.
[Eung Ryeong]
So. what are you planning now?
I believe what you're saying. comrade.
[clicks tongue]
And trust me. the missile intel
couldn't matter less to me.
That's why I'm trying to give you
a way out of this situation.
The money you moved through Macau
to finance operations against the South.
You converted eight million dollars
into casino chips
and stashed them in a private vault
at the Fanta Casino.
Just hand over the vault access card.
and I'll personally arrange for you
to stow away on a ship to another country.
[chuckles]
So my hunch was right after all.
That's the reason you kept me alive
despite the order they gave
to get rid of me.
The access card. Where do I find it?
If I turn the card over too soon.
I'd be losing my only leverage
in this negotiation.
I knew I had to be prepared
for this kind of situation.
so before coming down to the South.
I went to China and hid it.
Don't try to fool me!
This isn't a negotiation.
I can kill you right now
with official authorization.
I'm giving you one last chance.
Tell me now. Where's the access card?
[laughs]
I knew you'd come for me.
66 never disappoints.
66. you're… [coughs]
…the finest warrior of North Korea.
-I think that--
-Shut it.
If you want to live.
[chuckles]
I got the package.
They won't risk shooting.
Okay. No need to make a mess here.
We don't have much time.
Let's get started. Let's go. Chef.
Don't forget to report in.
Whew. that's quite a load today. Whew!
[exhales. grunts]
[groans]
Ah!
Laundry truck ready at the loading dock.
Come on. please hurry.
Hey! You guys from up north!
Hey. your security's been breached!
Getting in was way too easy. man.
We're here. so you're screwed. Get ready.
[Han-soo] Hey. Jin-cheol.
Rock and roll!
[Jin-cheol] Ah…
-[groans]
-[buzzer sounds]
You…
Don't forget. Each one of us
is taking 15. Keep track.
[Jin-cheol. agent screaming]
-Come on. demo team.
-I'll show you demo team.
[sighs] Mr. Kim.
we haven't secured the route yet.
The two agents are still there.
Surveillance. Any unusual activity?
Surveillance. Surveillance!
What are they doing?
Move. now!
Mr. Kim. they know we're here.
-They'll be there any second. Get out.
-What about you?
We don't have time to waste.
We'll move out. One minute.
Go check there!
[grunts]
He's already at the resort.
That motherfucker.
What is all this?
Three of them jumped us.
They suddenly showed up.
There's three of them. huh?
Secure our radio communications
and activate the jamming device. Now!
Yes. sir!
What are you doing?
Get the cameras back up! Now!
I'm on it. sir.
ACTIVATION READY
We need to cut off
all their communications.
Hey. Kim. are you there?
Do you still need more time--
-[feedback]
-[all groaning]
[groans]
What's going on?
What are you planning to do
now that we're cut off?
Hey. you guys know how to use a jammer?
A SIGNAL JAMMING DEVICE
USED TO DISRUPT GPS OR RADAR
That's how they start their attacks.
What the hell are you saying?
We've been under attack all night long.
[sighs] Come on.
we can end this right here.
Feels like the whole North is here.
-Yeah. bring it on!
-Just go away!
[all screaming]
[tense music plays]
[agents groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
Red alert! Red alert!
Unidentified hostile spotted.
Deploy reinforcement.
Unknown hostile in the fifth floor
emergency stairwell.
Oh. shit. the stairs.
[grunting]
System restored. sir.
Get the EMP ready.
A DEVICE THAT DISABLES ELECTRONICS
USING AN ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSE
-Sir?
-What part didn't you get?
-I did that.
-No. I took him down.
-I took him down.
-I know you've been cheating.
-I punched him first.
[both panting]
-Did we take 20 down?
-Yeah. that's what it looks like.
Let's just split it evenly.
We took down ten each. okay?
Okay. okay.
It's midnight. Let's just keep moving.
I'm sure Kim's out of there by now.
Oh. boy.
Whoa.
[tense music plays]
Are you late to class?
Why didn't you just show up
with the other guys?
While we're at it.
let's take 'em all down.
Overconfidence can get you in trouble.
[screams]
Jin-cheol. don't go alone…
You're outnumbered. you can't do it.
-Save your breath.
-Jin-cheol!
-Let fists do all the talking.
-This isn't working!
-Come on!
-[agents scream]
[sighs] I'll take the stairs.
Where the hell are these guys? Huh?
-Excuse me.
-Oh. yeah. yeah. hi.
Why are you still here?
Yeah. I'm sorry. I'm almost done.
Oh. damn.
Is that all you've got?
Bring it on! [laughs]
You weak fucker! [screams]
ELECTROMAGNETIC PULSE
What's the range of this thing?
All the power in the building
will be cut off if we do that. sir.
LOADING DOCK
Okay. okay. okay. Hey. wait.
Come on. Just let me talk.
[grunts] Man. just hear me out.
[security] Control room. control room.
Check zone one and the control room.
[footsteps running]
KITCHEN STORAGE
In there.
[agent 1] Did you find them?
[agent 2] I checked the hotel
reception hall. They're not there.
[agent 1] Where the hell
are those rats hiding?
[agent 2] So what do we do?
[agent 1] Damn it. Follow me.
Why aren't those guys coming out?
Where are they now? We had a plan!
[security] They're coming now.
-Oh.
-[security] Excuse me.
-You finished with the laundry pickup?
-Oh. yeah. I'm all finished here.
You may head home now.
Thanks for your services.
Oh. yeah. okay.
Uh. I really need to pee.
Just leave.
The hotel's having problems. sir.
For your own safety.
please leave immediately.
Oh. yeah. Can-- Can I-- I'll be quick.
I'm sorry. sir. Please leave right now.
Oh. uh. uh. I'll hold it
till I'm home. [chuckles]
Take it easy!
[sighs]
[engine starts]
[chuckles]
[agent 1] What? Is the power out?
-[agent 2] It's me.
-[agent 3] Turn on the light.
[agent 1] Lights. lights!
Hey. I wanted to talk.
[grunting]
The light!
Tae Geun here.
Jin Bok here.
Jin-cheol here.
Hwang Sun here.
[Tae-Geun] Get him!
-[punches landing]
-[grunting]
Where is that guy?
Where did he go?
[agents gasping]
Boys. I just wanted to talk.
Rock and roll!
[Jin-cheol grunts]
What are you waiting for?
I want you to kill those guys right now.
66 and Ri Eung Ryeong. both of them.
Shoot them on sight. Get going!
What the hell is going on?
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
Run.
You guys keep popping up like cockroaches.
What the hell. man?
I thought it might be you.
You haven't changed a bit.
Comrade Sung Han-soo.
Looks like the North and South
sports heroes are meeting again.
Sure. they all say I'm a hero.
but. uh. I'm not really sure who you are.
-Do I know you from somewhere?
-We competed in different sports.
but we ran into each other
at the Olympics. you know.
Spooky. Geez. I still don't know
who you are.
What sport did you compete in?
Gymnastics. didn't you? [chuckles]
Why don't we fight and you'll see?
I really don't care. Just tell me.
All right. You don't need to answer.
Hey. wait. You're fighting dirty.
Blinding the other guy?
You're good at talking. aren't you?
[chuckles] I'm even better
at kicking ass.
-Do it.
-[shouts]
-Ha!
-Geez…
[groaning]
[grunting]
[Kim] Min-ji's safety first.
so I'll get rid of you.
[laughs]
-[Kim] Beg my daughter for forgiveness.
-I'm very sorry.
[Kim] With a sincere heart.
[grunting]
[exhales heavily. grunting]
[straining]
Oh. look. short ribs.
Ah. of course.
I can tell by the movement of your--
your ears. I get it now.
You're Mr. Spandex.
I'm Jang Tae San.
gold medalist in wrestling.
Jang Tae San?
Wait. the Jang Tae San?
I didn't ask for your name.
I don't care. [chuckles]
This kitchen's pretty tight.
Your footwork is limited.
[scoffs] Want some? Here.
You see. I run a taekwondo studio.
And I give judo lessons. too.
-Do it.
-[Tae San shouts]
Now what?
Oh…
Oh. no. I can't just leave them.
I shouldn't go. I need to go back.
[groaning]
[agent grunting]
[gunshots]
[agent gasping]
[agent screams]
Come out.
[groaning]
[footsteps running]
[shushes]
[shouts]
What's that? Are you a blacksmith?
Just die!
Oh. shit. he's strong.
I am Jang Tae San.
I'm not impressed at all.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[groans]
How did I get myself into this?
-[grunts]
-[agent groans]
Boys. I just wanted
to get that off my chest.
Man. Park Jin-cheol's still got it.
This is the rock spirit!
I'm tired.
Stay right there!
You all know that I'll do it.
If any one of you move.
you're all gonna die.
[Han-soo] I'm hungry. too.
Let's just raid the kitchen.
[Jin-cheol] I don't care
if it's four servings or whatever.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
How'd you get free?
Man. he doesn't give up so easily.
You're untied! How did you manage?
-You did it wrong.
-You tied him up. No. wait. I did.
-Yeah.
-Hey. come here.
[Da-bin] Please. sir.
why are you doing this to us?
Please. sir. just let us go.
[Tae-hun] You better untie us right now!
[Da-bin] Please. sir. Please let us go.
Please let us go!
You piece of shit!
If you even lay a finger on me…
your kids are dead.
Jin-cheol. stop.
Now!
You…
If Da-bin gets harmed…
I'll chew up and spit out
every fucking bone in your body.
Our kids…
Where are they?
[sighs]
["Go! Go!" playing]
AGENT KIM REACTIVATED
[Han-soo] Kim. listen…
If you don't come…
our kids will die.
[Ju] If 66 dies. the kids will live.
What's there to decide?
I'll give you five more minutes…
[Kim] Protecting the people
you care about…
[Ju] Or I'll kill the kids myself.
then it will be your turn.
[Kim] My Min-ji…
Take care of her.
[Jang] Agent 66…
should die.